What?
Yesterday, it's sunny.
Now, it's a WINDSTORM!
How did THAT happen?
Hold on a second.
This all happened because of
your cake, didn't it Needy?!
Don't call me Needy!
LEAFY:
Calm DOWN!
What's wrong with calling you Needy, Needy?
Oh, so you want a slap fight now, don't you, Needy!?
Well, I can slap, TOO!
Uh-oh!
SNOWBALL:
She deserved it!
It was HER cake!
AHH!
♪ [INTRO PLAYS] ♪
Subtitles: Daniel Adam Valle
Gloop-gloop, doot-doot.
It's time for Cake at Stake for the Cherries.
♪ Da-da-da-da-da-da ♪
♪ Cake at Stake! ♪
There's eight of you now.
There will only be seven later.
Okay, so we got fourteen votes.
Well, I wanted to make an ice cream
cake, but I forgot the ice cream.
So I made a chunk of ice again.
NOOO!
BLAAAH!
OMPF! Overreacting!
JK! I have an ice cream cake.
If you get no cake, you leave BF Dream Island.
Pin, you have a Win Token.
Would you like to use it now?
Uh, no.
I mean there's nothing mean I-
Yeah, yeah, we know.
Bubble is at zero votes...
[DEEP VOICE]
AGAIN.
Ew, gross! A needle!
OMG! You don't like 'em?
I love Needies!
Don't slap me! I said, "NEEDLE"!
Now, I will say who else has zero votes.
Pen,
Pencil,
and Firey.
Hey! No fair!
Hey, where's my cake!?
Oh, oh, yeah, I forgot.
Hey!
Grr! I'm gonna crush you, Announcer Speaker thing!
Needle, what are you doing here?
You're on the other team.
Aw, seriously?
ANNOUNCER:
You four all got at least one vote.
Match and Eraser, you both got one vote, a pie-
I mean you both got one vote each.
Thank you!
- ANNOUNCER: Woody...
- WOODY: Ahh...
...is eliminated at nine votes.
HEAAAUUUGHUEAAAOOOH!
Sorry, Woody. You didn't not ain't
not get no any none of nothing.
Let's fling him to the TLC!
Wait, you always say "the TLC".
Is it an object?
You mean the Tiny Loser Chamber?
Duh! Of course it's an object.
WOODY:
HEEEAAAEEEAAAEEE!
FLOWER:
Uh-oh, It's CLOSING!
BLOCKY: Awh, why do we get only
five minutes of sunlight a day?
FLOWER:
Move over, Blocky!
I don't know about you,
Need-ULLLAAH,
but that bridge doesn't look so strong.
And I can't see the bottom of that gorge!
Go, Bubble!
Woi-huh-hoi-huh! Hey!
Yeah, SB!
Can you believe he didn't even try my cake?
You know, that's really mean...
Your tiny, teeny-tiny little brain...
[GOLF BALL GIBBERISH]
...I mean, I just don't understand!
Hold on, Coiny!
I've got some BUSINESS to take care of!
GB!
It's time to PAY!
HEUUGH!
Do do-do do, do do-do!
Oh! Oh, no!
Oh, no!
OEAAAH!
Bubble, gotcha!
I'm in an alliance! We have to stick TOGETHER!
Great! How do we cross without a bridge?
There's another one down there!
ERASER:
Oh.
Icy, do you still want revenge?
How's this?
I'll help you cross the bridge!
Needle, you, too!
Let's all go TOGETHER!
GOTCHA!
WAAAOOOAAOOOAAAAAOOUU!
Now, THAT was totally uncalled for.
You wanna go down there, too?!
Please, Snowball. Calm down.
THAT'S IT!
HOLD ON!
These dumb sticks are in the way!
Seriously?!
Pen, see any third bridge?
No, but the old bridge still has its rope railings.
We can climb down those!
ERASER:
There is no way I am doing that!
But don't you want to win and get Dream Island?
I DO! When I win, there will be
a big sign in front saying...
"PENISLAND", no spaces, all caps!
So let's do this!
Snowball, you're not gonna throw me off, are you?
No, Coiny. You're my friend!
What about Teardrop?
Well, as long as she doesn't say I'm bad...
SB? She can't talk.
Okay, Pen. You go first.
Ooh! Ah! Oh! Ah!
Hold on a second.
These are just black bendy straws attached with tape!
Wait, WHAT?!
AAAAAHHHHH!
Hold it! Hold it!
Since none of you crossed the bridge, and there
is no way the remaining six of you can cross,
it's a tie, zero to zero. So we need a tiebreaker.
Whichever team manages to rip their
team necktie first wins the contest.
Get it? Tie Breaker?
The Squashy Grapes win, so
one of the Cherries goes home.
There are seven Cherries to choose from.
Go ahead. Vote one off.
Hey, where's Golf Ball?
I thought she fell, too!
PEN:
Um, Match?
Golf balls... sink.
So do rocks.